I have a beautiful wife I am married
she's my best friend
I honestly feel I want to get too corny
here that we're gonna probably take our
last breaths together on this earth I
really feel that I don't know it's not
because of what you think it's because
we both have an anger problem we're
gonna kill each other at the same time
no I love my wife she is she's awesome I
have a woman I got from a Latin country
she's from Honduras yeah and wouldn't
you think if you get a woman from
Honduras she'd by default know how to
dance yeah just come with it right
you'll be my refrigerator it comes with
the door yeah nobody minds the
frigerators no door right well I modeled
I didn't buy a lab night
let's let's start over
what I'm trying to say is 13 years in I
realized my woman who's authentically
Latin like she comes from a Central
America cannot dance I have a defective
broken Latin woman
I'll give you an idea what she looks
like a few dances you know those things
they blow up on Saturdays in front of
car locks to get you to come in and buy
a car
gamora Tampa me on the dance floor yeah
you know you should put something hit
her mouth she's gonna bite her tongue
off we have a beautiful little 16 month
old baby girl at home yeah oh no she's
not mine Jesus oh she's no she's I'm in
love all over again she's six she's
sixteen months and her name is Denali
yeah a beautiful name
and there's the only thing I can tell
you about Denali when you take her
clothes off to dress her or change her
she loses her mind and she just starts
screaming at top her lungs she kicks her
legs just gets very violent and then she
goes number two we've taken her back to
the doctors and they're like well it's
not normal but it's not abnormal please
take her home but as her father I hope
this continues well into her 30s
[Music]
[Applause]
these little Punk's gonna come to my
door hey mr. Russell you want me to have
your daughter in by 9:00 nope
you can keep her all night son you bring
her back when you think she's ready to
come back she'll let you know
folks did you guys know that Drybar
comedy has its own app you can download
it right now and watch my whole special
in fact I have a little example see this
is a phone this is what we use now we're
all on it you're probably on it right
now watching this so go download the app